So that you can go home, or obviously you're at home, but so can start doing this tonight, the first thing that we'll do is build a scrap file.
To build a scrap file, you're going to need a supply of magazines that you don't care about, they're not the library's, they're your own that you can cut up.
Books, a good place, or you can go get books at a resell place, any place that has picture books, anything.
Anything that's visually appealing to you and visually stimulating that you can cut up, you're going to need to have that compiled in front of you, and then you start looking through those things.
Keep in mind you're going to be pulling design elements to create clothing, and the first part of that is drawing the actual female form, that the clothing is going to be displayed on.
And in order to do that you need to have images from several different categories.
The first thing you're going to need to do is have images of the full fashion figure, whether you're going to be menswear or women’s wear, I'm only going to talk about women’s wear, 'cause that's all I do.
So you need the full body, you need ads from magazines that are a full person.
Then you need ads that are close up of the head, that way you can see the details.
You want to get ads that are accessories; you're going to have accessories in your collection.
Belts, shoes, purses, whatever.
You want every single aspect of the form of the body that you can look at and begin to reference your own drawings from.